快看 走廊里
Look -- in the hallway!
有只鸟 有架飞机
It's a bird! It's a plane!
真是超上气不接下气啊
It's super-out-of-breath.
也祝你万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween to you, too.
对不起 我只是
I'm sorry. I'm just --
我很担心今天的结辩陈词
I'm really nervous about this closing argument today.
是因为你已经连输三个案子了吗
Is it because you've lost three cases in a row?
这么小声说也不会减轻痛苦的
Whispering it doesn't make it any less painful.
-抱歉 -好了
- Sorry. - Okay.
不是 是这个案子本身
No, it's just that this case --
很难维持陪审团的注意力
It's so hard to hold the jury's attention.
你要跟我排练一遍你的陈词吗
Well, do you want to run your argument by me?
-可以吗 -当然
- Could I? - Sure.
好
Um, okay.
六年前 阿尔杰证券公司
Six years ago, Alger Equities
从市政养老基金
took investments
和个人投资者获得投资
from municipal pension funds and private investors
然后将这些资金全部投向海外...
and funneled all of that into offshore --
你已经没在听我说了
And I've already lost you.
不 我是在想今天正好是万圣节
No. I was just thinking -- because it's Halloween,
你戴着这个出庭怎么样
what if you wore these in the courtroom?
向陪审团显示"看 我这人很幽默"
Show the jury "Hey, I'm playful."
小卡 我是律师
Cam, I'm an attorney,
不是在火车上躲猫猫的兔八哥
not Bugs Bunny trying to hide on a train.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
沃尔多来了
There's Waldo!
这次装扮服比赛我要赢了
I think I'm gonna win the costume contest.
亲爱的 赢不赢不重要
Hey, now, honey, it's not important if you win.
主要是好玩 来拍个照
It's just for fun. Picture.
但如果赢了就更好玩了
But it's more fun if you win.
无意冒犯 小爸
No offense, Daddy.
莉莉最近一直在暗示我
You know, Lily's been letting me know recently
她觉得被冷落了
that she's feeling neglected.
应该是因为我一心扑在橄榄球上
I think it's because of all my football stuff.
所以我这次卯足劲儿装扮她
That's why I went all out on her costume.
你看是不是一模一样
Look how incredibly accurate it is.
那小家伙在哪儿呢
Where is that little guy?
快点 快出现 快点
Come on. Come to me. Come on.
在...在这儿
Here you -- here you go.
无论他盯着沃尔多看多久
No matter how long he stares at it,
小卡就是找不到他
Cam cannot find Waldo.
太不可思议了
It's crazy.
有一次 他指着理发店外的旋转彩柱
O-once, he pointed to a barber pole,
我们就让他以为他找对了
and we just gave it to him.
那小家伙在哪儿
Where is the little guy?
就在这儿
He's right there.
你是怎么这么快找到...
How do you find it so...
你试试这个
Let's try these.
好了
Okay.
伙计们 你们觉得我今晚穿这身怎么样
Boys, what do you think about my costume for tonight?
看起来好极了 亲爱的
You look dynamite, honey.
谢谢 我是菲欧娜公主
Ay, thank you. I am Princess Fiona.
这样我要扮王子吗
So does that make me a prince?
我得一整晚都扶着个王冠吗
Do I have to keep track of a crown all night?
不 你扮史瑞克 那头怪物
No, you're Shrek, the ogre.
你是说那个绿怪物吗
You mean that big green thing?
不 我才不想一整晚都戴着
Nah, I don't want to walk around all night
丑兮兮的橡胶面具
with an ugly rubber mask.
不用 你只要把脸涂成绿色
No. You just need to paint your face green,
就可以了
and that's it.
你每次都这样
You do this every time.
你自己扮成公主 我就得扮成个怪物
You go as a princess. I have to go as some freak.
你当美女 我当野兽
You're beauty, I'm the beast.
你当碧昂斯 我就是...那谁
You're Beyonce? I'm...that guy.
你又不跟我一起去买装扮服
Well, you never want to go shopping with me for costumes,
所以我想买什么就买什么
so I get what I want,
你就得跟我配套
and you are what comes with it.
今年 我要自己打扮一套
Well, this year, I'm getting my own costume,
打扮得很健壮 充满男子汉气概
and it's gonna be tough and manly --
比如牛仔或者建筑工人
maybe a cowboy or a construction worker.
你知道
You know that
米奇和小卡去年就是那样穿的吧
that's what Mitch and Cam wore last year, right?
该死 我切到我的手指了
Damn it! I cut my finger!
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween.
我是说真的 我切到手指了 你看
No, really -- I cut myself. Look!
很逼真啊
That looks great.
那血是用什么弄的
What'd you use to make the blood?
用刀 我真的受伤了
A knife. I'm actually hurt.
水平很高嘛 亲爱的
Great production value, sweetheart.
了不起
I'm impressed.
难以置信万圣节我还得上班
Can't believe I've got to go to work on Halloween.
真讨厌
This blows!
别担心 你回家的时候
Don't worry.By the time you get home,
奇妙乐园就已经投入运作了
AwesomeLand will be up and running.
克莱尔今年工作很忙
Claire's busy with work this year,
所以由我来负责万圣节活动
so I'm taking over the halloween duties.
我的主题是奇妙乐园
My theme is AwesomeLand.
包含一切菲尔觉得很奇妙的东西
Which includes anything Phil finds awesome.
比如一把巨大的伞
It's a pretty big umbrella.
巨大的美丽的伞 简直太奇妙了
Big, pretty umbrellas -- those are awesome.
克莱尔喜欢血 内脏啊 暴力什么的
Claire loves blood and guts and gore,
但谁说万圣节一定要这么吓人
but who says Halloween has to be scary?
除了你之外的所有人
Everybody but you.
这简直要让她气死了
This is killing her.
至少有什么要死掉了
At least something's dying.
现在开庭
Court is now in session.
律师 准备好做结辩陈词了吗
Counselor, are you ready to deliver closing arguments?
是的 法官大人
Yes, your honor.
那就开始
Well, let's get --
等等 奥利呢
Wait. Where is Holly?
抱歉 法官大人 我的公交车晚了
Sorry, your honor. My bus was late.
律师 开始吧
Counselor, proceed.
好的
O-okay.
各位陪审团成员
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
这件案子的细节
the details of this case are --
复杂又充满专业术语
are complicated and technical,
但是对受害者有悲惨又深远的影响
but they have a, uh, a tragic and profound effect on the victims.
那个...
Uh, the, um...
养老金遭到滥用 生活被毁
pensions were squandered, lives were destroyed,
曾经很有前途的职业
and careers, once so promising,
现在全完了
were now...ruined.
因为这段婚姻
So, because of this marriage,
你基本上就是歌手夏奇拉的第三个表弟了
you're basically third cousins with Shakira.
我们没法拿到免费的演唱会门票
I mean, we don't get the free tickets,
但很好玩
but it's fun.
天啊 这是什么
Ay, dios mios. What is this?
怎么了公主 我是白马王子
What's up, princess? I'm Prince Charming.
我能看出来
I can see that.
我给乔准备了驴子装扮服
I got Joe a donkey costume,
给斯黛拉准备了猫耳
and I got Stella cat ears.
希望她不要追赶自己
I just hope she doesn't chase herself.
我懂 因为她是一只狗
Ah, I get it -- because she's a dog.
我还发现菲奥娜公主
I also found out that Princess Fiona
应该戴皇冠 所以给你
is supposed to wear a tiara, so here you go.
他们有一桶呢
They had a whole bucket full of 'em.
我好喜欢
I love it.
你看起来好帅
Ay, and you look so handsome.
像是你当海军时拍的照片上的样子
It's like those pictures of you in the navy.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
不如我们让乔睡个午觉
Why don't we put Joe down for a nap
然后我们也去休息会儿
and then we go and take a nap,
但不是去睡...
but not the one we sleep --
我明白 我加入
I got it. I'm in.
好
Okay.
你今天不是要开重大会议吗
Hey. I thought you had a big meeting.
是啊 但我把手机忘在家里了
I do, but I left my cellphone here.
我需要在红灯时用手机阅读
I need it to read at stoplights
这样就不会乱想了
so I don't think about stuff.
抱歉 这太荒唐了
I'm sorry, but that's ridiculous.
亲爱的 这好像不大合适
Ohhh. Honey, I don't think that fits.
在奇妙乐园里就很合适
It fits in AwesomeLand.
这是魔法帽
It's a magic hat.
我会让这只兔子从里面跳出来
I'm gonna have this bunny jumping out of it.
你要在里面放点血吗
You gonna put some blood on it,
也许掉出一个眼球
maybe dangle an eyeball?
谁伤害了你啊
Who hurt you?
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
我知道是杰和迪迪
I know it's Jay and Dede.
总之 我得去取装扮服了
Anyway, I got to go get my costume.
看在老天的份上
Oh, for god's sake.
我亲我妈都比那有激情
I kiss my mom hotter than that.
是的 我见过
He does. I seen it.
我们的新邻居
Our new neighbors,
医用大麻零售商罗尼和他老婆安布尔
medical-marijuana retailer Ronnie and his wife, Amber,
两个月前搬了过来
moved in two months ago, and --
才一周半啦
It's been a week and a half.
天啊 真的吗
Dear god. Really?
是啊
Yeah.
我不明白
I don't get it.
一个巨型纸杯蛋糕有什么吓人的
What's scary about a giant cupcake?
今年我们不玩吓人的
We're not doing scary this year.
提醒一下
Well, heads up --
我们要举行吓出屎来的恐怖比赛
we're doing crap-your-pants scary on account of the contest,
希望不会冒犯到糖果乐园的你们
so I just hope we don't offend you over here in candy land.
什么比赛
What contest?
这是我们在之前的社区组织的比赛
Oh, it's something we started in the old neighborhood.
如果你想加入 就交20块
If you're into it, you, uh, chip in 20 bucks,
街上最吓人的房子获得奖金[大麻]
and scariest house on the street wins the pot.
不是真的大麻啦
Not actual pot.
我需要处方才能给你拿
I'd have to see a prescription for that.
等等 你不是警察...
Wait. You're not a cop --
我都说了12次了 我不是警察
No, for the 12th time, I'm not a cop.
你们的装饰
Well, you are not gonna offend me
不会冒犯到我
with your little decorations.
要知道这一切都是菲尔搞的
Please know that this... is Phil.
要我来负责 一切都会很可怕的
When I'm in charge, it's terrifying.
我相信你会别着一个写着"呸"的胸针
I'll bet you give all the other soccer moms
把别的"孩奴"妈妈吓一跳
a good scare with that pin that says "Boo."
你真走运我今天要去上班
You are so lucky that I have to go to work today,
否则我会让你见识一下什么叫吓人
or I would show you scary.
我会赢得你的小比赛
I would win your little contest.
你不知道你的对手有多强大
You don't know what you're up against.
我们不会让孕妇或者有心脏病的人
We don't let preggos or people with heart trouble
经过我家大门
past our front gate.
几年前
Couple years ago,
我们吓得一个人进了医院 他差点吓死
we scared a man Into the hospital almost to death.
既然你有借口 公主
Well, since you got an excuse, princess,
看来我的连胜纪录会保持
looks like my winning streak will carry on.
也许我们家的老房子也能赢呢
Might even win at the old house, too.
那地方挺吓人的
We left that place pretty scary.
我要去跟一个朋友喝咖啡
I'm meeting a friend for coffee.
不行
No, you're not. No.
你要帮我把这些都弄倒
You're helping me take this all down.
全都拿开
Everything goes.
除了兔子
Everything except the bunny.
我对兔子有安排
I have plans for the bunny.
好了 数到三 说"啊"
Okay! On three, say "Argh!"
-一 二 三 -啊
- Argh One, two, three! - Argh Argh!
太棒了
Oh, that's great.
谢谢 你俩是什么关系
Thank you. And how are you two related?
知道吗 不管是异性恋还是同性恋
Uh, you know what -- gay or straight,
都可以组建家庭 所以...
there's no wrong way to make a family, so...
好了 别激动
Okay, down, girl.
我是说 你俩扮演的角色有什么关系
I meant, how are your costumes related?
这是亲子装扮服比赛
It's a parent/child costume contest.
是吗
It is?
传单上都写得清清楚楚了
It was all clearly stated on the flier.
还有传单吗
There was a flier?
我给你看了 大爸
I gave it to you, daddy!
我就知道你的装扮服都搞错了
I knew your costume was all wrong!
好吧 别慌张
O-okay, hey, don't panic.
游行之前还有很多时间
There's plenty of time before the parade.
《寻找沃尔多》里面还有什么人物
Is there another character in "Where's Waldo?"
白胡子巫师
Wizard Whitebeard.
那就扮这个了 会很有意思的
Okay! Well, that'll be fun!
我上次跟白胡子一起出去玩
I haven't gone out with a Whitebeard
还是带我表妹莎莉去舞会的时候
since I took my cousin Sally to the prom.
好了 我尽快回来
All right, I'll be back as soon as I can.
莉莉 解释一下大爸的梗
Lily, explain daddy's joke.
我喜欢有头发 我知道怎么物尽其用
I loved having hair, and I knew how to use it.
我可以走到美女面前
I'd walk up to a pretty girl
捋一下头发
and run my hand through my hair.
停下摩托车 摘掉头盔
Score a touchdown, whip the helmet off,
捋一下头发
run my hand through my hair.
有人说人靠衣装
People say clothes make the man,
其实根本不是这回事
but that makes no sense.
男人的精髓在于一头浓密的靓发
What makes the man is a nice head of hair.
该死 感觉好像我的头发还在一样
Damn it! It's like a phantom limb!
不行 不行
No. No!
这一点都不像真的
This doesn't look real at all.
艾丽克斯 你早上
Alex, where's that blood
涂在手指上的血是哪儿来的
you were using this morning on your finger?
在我血管里流着呢 好让我活着
Running through my veins, keeping me alive.
老爸回来了
Here comes dad.
他肯定会喊
He's gonna be all like,
不 你们干了什么
"No! What did you do?!
奇妙乐园哪去了
Where's AwesomeLand?!"
不 你们干了什么 奇妙乐园哪去了
No! What did you do?! Where's AwesomeLand?!
你是来自未来的人吗
Are you from the future?
菲尔 亲爱的 亲爱的
Phil, honey, honey,
计划有一点小小的改变
w-we've had a little change of plans.
为什么
Why?
你怎么在这
What are you even doing here?
不是要上班吗
Shouldn't you be at work?
那个超讨人厌的罗尼
That obnoxious Ronnie was worried
觉得我的装饰比不过他
that I wouldn't be able to handle his decorations,
因为他想赢
'cause he's trying to win
"这条街最可怕的房子"比赛
this "Scariest house on the street" contest,
我就说 老娘不仅要装饰得比你好
and I was like, "Not only can I handle your decorations.
还要赢得比赛
I'm gonna win that contest."
所以 欢迎来到地狱疯人院
So welcome to the insane asylum from hell.
我现在的感觉就像在地狱
That's what it feels like.
来嘛 很好玩的
Come on. It's gonna be fun.
孩子们扮精神错乱的病人
The kids are gonna be deranged mental patients,
我来当虐待狂护士
and -- and I am going to be a sadistic nurse,
你就是神经病医生
and you are a demented doctor.
20年来你都不同意
20 years of "No,"
为了这破比赛 你就愿意穿护士装了吗
but for this, you'll dress like a nurse?!
恶心
Um, no.
女的就该当护士 男的就该当医生
Of course the woman is the nurse and the man is the doctor.
这种重男轻女的思想 才可怕
That kind of thinking -- that's what's scary.
别说了 节日都被糟蹋了
Tap out. It's a holiday.
我花了那么多时间和精力来装饰
You know, I put a lot of time and energy into my thing,
你就这样全给毁了 就为向我们不熟
but you just shut it all down to prove something
甚至根本不喜欢的人证明自己
to people that we barely know and don't even like!
菲尔 罗尼取笑了你的奇妙乐园
Phil, Ronnie made fun of Awesomeland.
他叫它"糖果乐园"
He called it "Candy Land".
那又怎样
So?
傻瓜镇 蠢蛋村
Stupidville? Dumbburgh?
谁管他怎么想
Who cares what he thinks?!
你什么时候在乎一下我的想法
Maybe someday you'll care what I think.
菲尔
Phil...
宝贝 看
Well -- honey, look!
你的兔子我还留着
I kept your bunny!
小啃啃你怎么了
Nibbles!
终于赶上了
Made it in the nick of time.
趁我还是四千岁
All right, let's get this parade started
让游行开始吧
while I'm still just 4,000 years old.
你知道游行要放学后才开始吧
You do know the parade's not till after school, right?
什么 我不知道
What? No!
我待不了那么久 我有球队训练
I can't stay that long. I have football practice.
我的天 我得去告诉莉莉
Oh, my god. I have to tell Lily.
她肯定会很伤心
She's gonna be devastated.
哦不
Oh, no.
沃尔多在哪里
Where's Waldo?
游行什么时候变成放学后才开始了
Since when has the parade been after school?
一直都是 传单上写了
Since always. It was on the flier.
单子有多大
How big was this flier?
现在我们改用视频聊天了吗
Oh, so this is how we call each other now?
米奇尔 我出了个装扮服状况
Mitchell, I have a costume emergency.
自信地穿上吧
Just wear it with confidence,
小卡 你穿着会很帅的
Cam. I'm sure you look great.
不是 我找不到莉莉了
No, I can't find Lily!
找到了 在垃圾桶边
Oh, okay, found her -- by the trash can,
旁边有个穿得像流浪汉的大个子小朋友
next to the big kid dressed like a hobo.
还好你找到了
Oh, you did it.
那个好像不是小朋友
I don't -- I don't think that's a kid.
我得找个大人说一下
I should probably tell a grown-up.
你真无法想像这里的状况
Well, you have no idea what's happening here.
速记员穿得像蜘蛛
The stenographer is dressed like a spider.
所有人都没在听我陈述
I cannot get anyone to listen to anything I'm --
米奇尔 回头说
Mitchell, I can't.
莉莉
Lily?
宝贝 听我说
Honey, listen.
大爸参加不了游行了
Daddy can't stay for the parade.
你答应过我的
But you promised!
我知道 可是游行开始得太晚
No, I know I did, but it starts later than I thought,
我必须去
and I have to get to...
橄榄球训练 行 你走吧
Football practice! It's fine! Just go!
别走 莉莉 等等我
No, Lily! Wait!
这下我又找不到她了
Well, she's gone forever.
歌洛莉亚 我头发去哪了
Gloria, what happened to my hair?
拜托 咱们不说这行不
Ay, no. Please. I cannot have this conversation again.
是的 杰 时间就是杀猪刀
Yes, Jay, time is cruel.
我扮白马王子的假发 不见了
My Prince Charming wig -- it's gone.
你们觉得哪个好
Okay, what do you think --
帅气夏威夷人还是性感苏格兰人
Handsome Hawaiian or sexy Scotsman?
现在没时间跟你说
I can't do this right now.
拜托 杰
Come on, Jay --
这可是我最后一次
this is my farewell tour
在邻里间玩"不给糖就捣乱"
of trick-or-treating in the neighborhood.
我的造型必须要很抢眼
I have to go out strong.
还是我应该扮成别人所期待的那样呢
Or should I just do what people are expecting?
别去要糖吃 因为你已经二十岁了
Stay home 'cause you're 20?
杰 不要对曼尼这么刻薄
Jay, please don't be mean to Manny.
可能是斯黛拉把你的假发
Maybe Stella took your wig
叼到后院埋起来了
and buried it in the yard.
之前我看到她在玩那个
I saw her playing with it earlier.
什么 你为什么不把它抢过来
What? Why didn't you take it from her?
我不了解你们之间的关系
I don't understand your relationship with her.
你还让她舔你的脚
You let her lick your feet.
那有什么关系
Who is that possibly hurting?
我现在该怎么办
What am I gonna do now?
白马王子是有头发的
Prince Charming had hair!
得了吧 这事我们又不能确定
Please. We don't really know that for sure.
那个时候又没有照相机
There weren't cameras back then.
也许就是因为他光头才必须要更迷人呢
Maybe he had to be charming because he was bald.
你觉得把你未成年女儿
You really think it's appropriate
绑在医用轮床上合适吗
to be strapping your teenage daughter to a gurney?
只要能赢就行
If we win, it is.
待会我要去厕所
I may have to take a pee break soon.
在这 用这个便盆
Ooh. Here. Use this bedpan.
我开玩笑的 那多恶心
I'm kidding. That's gross.
我把糖放在里面 拿着
I put candy in it. Here.
卢克
Luke.
Luke!
我刚才好像睡着了
I think I fell asleep.
这玩意就像自闭症专家发明的拥抱机器
This thing is like a Temple Grandin hug.
海莉宝贝 衣服穿反了
Haley, sweetie, uh, gown's on backwards.
没有 这样更可爱
Oh, no. It's cuter this way.
性感的人也会发疯 知道吗
Sexy people go crazy, too, you know.
去看看《人物》杂质上的报道
Read a People magazine.
菲尔
Phil.
你连试都不试一下你的医生服装吗
You're not even gonna try on your doctor costume?
是的
Nope.
但我们要赢了
But we're gonna win.
这难道不会让你感到高兴吗
Doesn't that make you happy?
我看起来像高兴吗
Do I look happy?
你有麻烦了 女士
You got a problem, lady.
这种暗黑恐怖的偏执感
This obsessive need to be dark and scary --
你自己根本都停不下来了
you can't even stop yourself.
我什么时候想停 就会停
I can stop whenever I want.
我无法融入这种气氛
Well, I'm not getting sucked in.
我要过自己想过的万圣节
I'm having the Halloween that I wanted.
这些都是什么
What is all this?
这是要表现得很滑稽吗
Is this supposed to be funny?
不 应该是很可怕
No, it's supposed to be scary.
不 应该是很奇妙
No, it's supposed to be awesome.
知道吗 其实我看得出来
You know, I could tell that you guys
你们并不喜欢我们搬过来
didn't love us moving in next door.
可能因为罗尼是卖大麻的
Maybe 'cause Ronnie deals pot
也可能因为我的星条旗比基尼
or maybe 'cause of my confederate-flag bikini.
我不知道 但是
I don't know, but --
但是我以为我们在慢慢成为朋友
But I thought we were becomin' friends.
我还准备邀请你们一起过感恩节 可是
I was gonna propose a joint Thanksgiving, but...
这招简直太低级了
This is really low.
不 亲爱的 没事的
No, honey, it's okay.
不 怎么会没事 罗尼
No, it's not okay, Ronnie!
这太无礼 也太残忍了
It's rude and it's cruel!
真希望我们的老房子还在
I wish we had our old house
这样就能马上把家开走
so we could drive it away
开得越远越好[房车]
as far as possible!
天哪 这是演的哪一出
Oh, my goodness. What was that?
安布尔对这事很敏感
Amber gets touchy about this stuff.
她...
Uh, she --
她在内华达州的一间疯人院待过半年
she spent six months in a cuckoo farm in Nevada.
对不起 我这样说她会生气的
I'm sorry. She gets mad when I say that.
是在犹他州
It was in Utah.
天哪
Oh, my god.
我们真的不知道 我发誓
We -- we had no idea. I swear.
没关系
I-it's cool.
我会给她一盒嘎吱船长麦片
I'll just...give her a box of Cap'n Crunch
再把她放到鱼缸前面
and set her in front of the fish tank.
那会让她平静下来
That seems to calm her down.
-好吧 -好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
我们得清理掉这些 我们得清理掉这些
We have to shut it down. We got to shut it down.
她说"感恩节一起过"[大麻烟卷感恩节]
Now, when she said "Joint thanksgiving,"
你觉得她是不是指...
do you think that she meant --
-不是 -好吧
- No. - Okay.
每一间公司
Each of these companies
都把未上报的资金存入同一个账户
funneled unreported funds into the same account.
我相信这张图表可以使这个
Now, I believe this chart makes clear
复杂骗局的网络清晰化
the intricate web of deceit.
好的 我听到了
Okay, I heard it.
我 我重新叙述一遍
I'm -- I'm gonna rephrase that.
这些公司密谋
These companies conspired
欺骗众多的无辜民众
to defraud numerous innocent people,
还有国内收入署
not to mention the Internal Revenue Service.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
法官阁下 可以上前吗
Your honor, may we approach?
如果你一定需要的话
If you must.
你看到这里发生了什么 对吧
You see what's happening here, right?
你连续输五场官司了
You're losing your fifth case in a row?
四场
Fourth. And --
谁说的 我要输了吗
Who said -- am I losing?
我认为 陪审团
Um, I just feel that the -- the jury
会被那个分散注意力 你知道的
might be a little bit distracted by, um...you know.
记录员请记录下来 辩方律师
Please let the record show that counsel is nodding his head
朝法庭速记员奥利点头
towards the court stenographer, Holly.
法官阁下 辩方律师是想抓住
Your honor, opposing counsel's
最后一棵救命稻草
grasping at straws
因为他又要输了
because he's losing again.
拜托 拜托
Oh, come on! Come on!
她穿得像个大蜘蛛
She's dressed like a giant spider!
我需要陪审团集中注意力到案情上
I need the jury to focus on the details of this case,
而不是这身奇装异服
not some ridiculous costume.
抱歉 你可能是个很好的人
I'm sorry. You're probably a very nice person.
好吧
Very well.
奥利 你能把装扮去掉吗
Holly, would you please remove the costume?
谢谢
Thank you.
女士们先生们 很抱歉要延时了
Ladies and gentlemen, I apologize for the delay.
根据律师要求
At the request of counsel,
法庭速记员将脱去装扮
the court stenographer will now remove the costume.
这个红头发真扫兴
That redhead's no fun.
他们讨厌你
They hate you.
根据我之前所说
A-as I was saying, um,
这些公司窃取了无数无辜民众的钱
these companies stole from countless innocent people,
各位知道
and, you know,
如果有人像那样伸手掏我的蛋
if someone had dipped into my nest egg like that, uh...
我肯定会怒不可遏
I'd be awful grouchy.
连输第四场
Number four.
给你
Here you go.
你扮的是什么[你本来应该怎样]
What are you supposed to be?
生在别人家里
Born into another family.
她扮的是苔丝·麦克吉尔
She is Tess McGill,
八十年代经典《打工女郎》里的
feminist heroine from te 1980s classic
女权主义者
"Working Girl".
有机会要去看看哦
You should check it out sometime.
过几年吧
In a few years.
有用吸尘器吸小鸡鸡的镜头
There is some light vacuuming in underpants.
继续努力
Keep up the good work!
这边情况如何
How's it going here?
我看起来很蠢
I look stupid!
这些小狗狗让我没法
These puppies are making it impossible
再生你的气
for me to stay mad at you.
愚蠢又可爱的狗狗们
Stupid, adorable puppies.
欢迎来到奇妙乐园
Welcome to AwesomeLand,
这里你唯一需要害怕的是乐趣本身
where the only thing to fear is fun itself.
克莱尔 我知道这不是你想要的万圣节
Claire, I know this isn't the Halloween you wanted,
可你能至少做个样子吗
but can you try to sell it?
对不起 亲爱的
I'm sorry, honey.
我冲你发火 还伤害了安布尔
I got mad at you and I upset Amber,
就因为罗尼叫我"孩奴"
and all because Ronnie called me a soccer mom.
我是什么毛病
What is wrong with me?
你没病
Nothing.
我也很讨厌别人胡乱下一些
I hate it when people assume things about me
错误的结论
that aren't true --
比如因为我漂亮 我就一定很傲慢
Like because I'm pretty, I'm stuck-up.
要是有人那么对我 我就会说
When people do that to me, I'm just like,
闭嘴 混蛋 我为什么要跟你说话
"Shut up, troll. Why am I even talking to you?"
我不喜欢被人分类
I do not like being pigeonholed.
很明显 妈妈
It's obvious, mom --
你通过万圣节来告诉大家你也是很犀利的
You use Halloween as a way to show people you have edge.
就像会计师买了台哈雷机车
It's like accountants who buy a harley.
她说得对
She's right.
扮恐怖就是我那部机车
Being scary is my motorcycle.
这才是我的苔丝
That's my Tess.
我的告别之旅可能带了太多情绪
I knew my farewell tour would be emotional,
但至少我做能说自己做到了我想做的
but at least I can say I did it my way.
你已经说了四遍了
You've said that four times.
你知道他别的歌吗
You know he had other songs?
妆化得不错 是富兰克林吧
Nice costume. Ben Franklin, right?
你开什么玩笑 这是白马王子
What? No! Prince Charming.
好吧
Oh. Sorry.
我以为白马王子是有头发的
I guess I just picture Prince Charming with hair.
我也这么认为 但是我的假发丢了
We all do, but I lost my wig,
我头发也掉光了
And I don't have any, so...
好吧 其实有些
Well, you know, there are
好方法是可以治谢顶的
some pretty effective solutions for that.
-你在说植发 -对啊
- Talking about hair plugs? - Yeah.
从两边和脑勺取一点移到头顶
Take some from the side and the back, right?
你觉得那对我有用吗
You think that would work for me?
应该会
It could.
但是你最好咨询一下真正的医生
But you might want a second opinion from an actual doctor.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你刚才和这个装医生的讨论植发吗
Did you just ask that fake doctor about hair plugs?
没有 你知道你的英文不太好
No! You know how you struggle with the language.
-杰 -该死 歌洛莉亚
- Jay. - Damn it, Gloria.
我很怀念有头发的日子
I miss having a head full of hair.
还有不要表现得好像你不希望我有头发
And don't act like you don't miss it, too.
我们结婚的时候
When we got married,
你就比现在多了四根头发
you had four more hairs than you do now.
你这个样子我一点都不吃惊
This is not a surprise to me.
那今天早些时候呢
What about today? Hmm? Earlier?
我们没在打盹的时候
When we were not napping?
当你性致高昂的时候
When you were a little extra-enthusiastic?
那是因为你兴致高
Because you were enthusiastic.
你给我们所有人买了万圣节装扮
You went out and bought costumes for all of us,
你还在唱歌
you were singing.
至少这次你没有说"我才没兴趣呢"
For once, you were not like, "I don't want to do this.
我只想在家里边看高尔夫球
"I just want to sit at home, watch golf,
边吃我的墨西哥式十层开胃菜
And eat my 10-layer dip."
五层 只有五层
Just five. Five layers.
一层就足够了 杰
One layer is enough, Jay.
我超爱你和我们一起玩
I loved that you were having fun with us.
一个快乐的老公
A happy husband --
对我来说才是最性感的
that's what is sexy to me.
所以你不觉得我像富兰克林吗
So you don't think I look like Ben Franklin?
对了 原来是他
Oh, yes! That's who it is!
一百美金钞票上那个男人 我的最爱
The man from the $100 bill -- my favorite!
好吧 万圣节快乐
All right, Happy Halloween.
那就是你的万圣节装扮吗 一个大鼻子
That's your costume? A big nose?
听着 别说那么多废话
All right, you know, cool it.
我今天过得很惨
I've had a rough day.
你以为你是我今天见的第一个海绵宝宝吗
You think you're the first SpongeBob I've seen?
要错过万圣节的欢乐了
I'm missing Halloween.
亲 如果大爸五分钟之内不回来的话
All right, honey, if daddy's not home in five minutes,
我就带你去要糖好不
I will take you trick-or-treating, okay?
我回来了
Okay! I made it!
橄榄球训练延时了 亲爱的
Football practice ran late, sweetie.
再给我两分钟 我很抱歉
Just give me two minutes. I'm so sorry.
随便
Whatever.
我敢说套装糖果肯定都发光了
I bet all the full-size candy bars are gone.
-莉莉 -不 不
- Lily. - Nope, nope.
她有权生气 米奇尔
She has every right, Mitchell.
我让橄榄球吞噬了我的生活
You know, I've let football consume my life,
我疏漏了对我而言最宝贵的东西
And I fumbled what's most valuable to me,
现在 我卡住了
And now I'm stuck!
能不能来个人帮帮我啊
Can somebody please help me?
-别去帮他 -够了 你们两个
- Don't help him! - Oh, enough, you two!
简直跟《八月: 奥色治郡》电影里一样混乱
It's like "August: osage county" Up in here.
-好了 你得... -我的头呢
- All right, you -- - Where's my head?
就在这儿 等一下 冷静 好吗
It's right here. Stop. Just calm down. Okay.
你别再自责不已了 好吗
You need to let yourself off the hook, all right?
你又不是抛弃她 自己去玩了
You didn't abandon her playing craps.
你是要去工作
You had to go to work.
他只顾着工作
He's always working.
不 他...
No, he's --
他并没有只顾着工作啊 莉莉
He is not always working, Lily.
证物A 你的上衣
Exhibit "A" -- your shirt,
他可是熬夜缝了一晚上
which he stayed up all night sewing
才让你穿上这完美的装扮服
so that you would have the perfect costume.
证物B
Exhibit "B" --
你的眼镜 他在易趣网上淘了两小时
Those glasses--two hours on eBay.
证物C 你的小背包
Exhibit "C" -- your satchel.
那是二爸读大学时用的挎包
Daddy's man purse from college
他翻了10个杂物箱才找到的
that he had to dig through 10 boxes to find,
因为二爸藏着不想让他找到
because daddy hid it from him.
但他没看那个传单啊
But he didn't read the flier!
我没有看
I never read it
是因为我根本没见到
Because I never saw it!
-你没见到那张传单吗 -没有
- You didn't see the flier? - No!
或许是因为你根本没收到
Maybe that's because you never got it.
我来向你呈上 那张传单
I submit to you...the flier...
根本没被贴到冰箱上
which never made it onto the refrigerator,
你本该把重要文件都贴在那里的
where you are supposed to put things,
因为它...
because it wa-a-a-s....
它...在...
It...was...
找到
Yes.
莉莉 你大爸或许错过了游行
Lily, your daddy may have missed the parade,
但他真是为万圣节用尽了心思
but he was all over Halloween.
我的陈述终止
I rest my case.
对不起 大爸
I'm sorry, daddy.
我也该说对不起
I'm sorry, too.
我成功胜诉
I got my win.
如果陪审团里都是
Trials would be a whole lot easier
像莉莉这样的7岁小女孩
if juries were made up of
那庭审就简单多了
7-year-old girls, like Lily.
或者像小卡那样的
And Cam.
我知道那不是重点
I know it's not the point,
但我们原本肯定会赢的
but we totally would've won.
你在道歉时最好别提这句
Might want to leave that out of your apology.
你们好啊
Howdy!
嘿 罗尼 你还好吗
Hey, Ronnie. What's up?
罗尼 我在找安布尔呢
Ronnie, hi. Um, I was looking for Amber.
她在里面呢
Oh, she's inside.
不 我不在
No, I ain't!
别闹了 安布尔
Knock it off, Amber!
安布尔 你好
Amber, hi.
听着 我想道个歉
Um, listen, I wanted to apologize.
我之前完全不知道你过去的经历
I had no idea about your history,
我太不懂得照顾你的情绪了
and I was being insensitive,
所以我希望我们能重新和睦相处
so I was hoping we could start over.
真的好温暖人心啊
That's really sweet.
都让我为编造那事感到愧疚了
Almost makes me feel bad for making the whole thing up.
什么
What?!
骗到啦
Trick!
她根本没被关进过疯人院
She never been to a nuthouse.
不是吧
No!
是啊 我才没疯呢
Yeah, I ain't crazy.
我倒是进过几次戒毒所
I mean, I've been to rehab a few times,
但那最多算是薪资照拿的度假
but that was just for paid vacation.
你撒谎 就是为了让我感到愧疚吗
You lied just to make me feel bad?
不不 我们撒谎
No, no -- we lied
那样我们的"僵尸妓女屋"就能获胜了
so that we could win with our zombie house o' whores!
真是太没有下限了
That is so messed up.
你刚刚说的是"妓女"还是...
Did you say "Whores," Or --
不不 那可不叫没下限
No, no. It ain't messed up.
本来的说法就是"不给糖就捣蛋"
The saying is "Trick or treat."
我们这玩的就是"捣蛋"
This is the trick part.
我们的院子里都是死妓女
Our yard's full o' dead whores.
你的院子里却是圣诞老人
You got a santa.
好吧 我听清了 是妓女
Yep -- "Whores." I heard it again.
我们何不谈谈这个呢
Why are we not talking about this?
总有一天 你们会为此付出代价的
There will come a day when you will pay for this.
你们不知道是什么时候
You won't know when,
也不知道是什么方式
and you won't know how,
但你们会亲身感受到的
but you will feel it.
那个小妞好吓人
That chick is scary.
谢谢
Thank you.
你完全无法想象
You have no idea.
厂家故意画的让你找不到他
You know, they just make it impossible to find him.
那很残忍 也很不合适
It's cruel and inappropriate.
那让孩子们注定只能失败
It just sets children up to fail,
那会摧毁他们的自尊心
and it destroys their self-esteem.
-就在那儿 -在吗
- Right there. - Is he there?
在哪儿呢
Is -- where --
她刚刚指的哪儿 指的哪儿啊
Where did she point? Where did she p--
现在我看上去像歌手罗德·斯图尔特了
Now I look like Rod Stewart.
谢你了啊
Thanks a lot.
我有着商业的头脑 诱人犯罪的身体
I have a head for business and a bod for sin.
是啊 没错
Yes, you do.
真恶心 这可是公共区域呢
Ew! This is a common area!